Guide to the Jock Elliott Papers, 1945-2005 and undated, bulk 1961-1982 RL.00359
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1984-1988 and undated, 1 Box
  - Originals [Closed to research]
    - Cine Metric, Jock Elliott, Hall of Fame, 1984. TRT: 1:30. Format: Umatic. (Box 21)
    - Hall of Fame on Jock, undated. TRT: approx. 5:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Institute of Directors Annual Conference, 1987. TRT: 37:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Institute of Directors Annual Conference, 1987. TRT: 37:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Institute of Directors Annual Conference, 1987. Reskilling Britain. TRT: 37:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Institute of Directors Annual Conference, 1987. TRT: 37:00. Format: VHS (NTSC Submaster). (Box 21)
    - Iphigene, A New York Times History Production, 1986. TRT: 19:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Jock Elliott, S. Kahn, Kelleher, undated. TRT: approx. 10:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - Wedding of Two Careers, Jock and Elly Elliott, 1988. TRT: approx. 60:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
    - WNET, Gala of Stars, 1986. Tape 1: Acts 1-4. TRT: 120:00. Format: VHS (Box 21)
    - WNET, Gala of Stars, 1986. Tape 2: Act 5. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS. (Box 21)
- Oversize Materials 1961-2002 and undated, 2 Boxes
  Consists of large-format items removed from previous series. Includes magazine clippings, newspaper clippings related to Elliott's 1986-1987 visit to Argentina, full issues of Advertising Age, proofs of an article about David Ogilvy, and proofs of posters for a fire safety advertising campaign. Items are arranged by their original series.
  - Clippings (Box 22)
    - Advertising Age, 1961-2002 (Box 22)
    - Argentina visit, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
    - Christmas books publicity, 1999, 2002 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous magazine clippings, 1963-1990 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence
    - London talk, 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Memorabilia
    - Blue Ribbon Selection Committee Appreciation Award, undated (Box 22)
  - Printed Materials
    - Ad Council bulletins, undated (Box 22)
    - Advertising Age, full issue, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Flagbearer, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Memorabilia (Box 23)
    - Elliott 60th Birthday, 1981
      - Commemorative binder (Box 23)
      - Loose items (Box 23)
  - Clippings--Confessions of a Magazine Reader, 1965 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Correspondence--Fire advertisement, 1969 (Oversize-folder 2)